[Music]
as a Prudential agent I have the
privilege of supporting the dreams of
people from all walks of life
for the mother-to-be when nothing is
more important than the child within I
support her dreams for a bubbly little
fella
with bright eyes cute little feet and
yes good health and for the parent who's
concerned about the future of his kids I
support his dream that they will grow up
to be the bestest most awesomest person
ever yeah and once he's able to see that
he can finally learn to let go for the
young man who's gotten some bumps and
bruises but also the willpower to rise
above it all I support his dream to keep
going even when the going gets tough for
those going through a rough patch in
life where hope is tested
I support the dream that they can
weather the storm and together as a
family
beat the odds look at that there's no
greater reward
[Music]
and for that someone somewhere out there
whose dreams barely exist anymore
because they are unwell and feel
insecure
I support the a dream to live life to
the fullest once more
so you see these dreams no matter what
form they take and how they change as a
Prudential agent
I'm here to support them
because dreams they keep us going
they give us hope
you
[Music]